[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
- What now?
- I have to make pee-pee.
(Leslie:)I'm sorry
about all of Sheldon's interruptions.
(Leonard:)He can be a bit of an eccentric.
If by "eccentric"...
...you mean "passive-aggressive
East Texas blowhole," I agree.
(Leonard:)Well, I think tonight
was a very good start.
(Leslie:)Me too. You're sure you're okay
postponing intercourse...
(Leslie:)...until our relationship
is past the initial viability test?
(Sheldon:)No problem.
I'm very skilled at postponing intercourse.
(Leonard:)I guess I'll call you
and we'll arrange another evening.
(Leslie:)I believe protocol dictates
that you wait a minimum of 18 hours...
(Leslie:)...before you call so I'm not repulsed
by your cloying eagerness.
(Leonard:)- Sure.
- Again, it's your decision. You're the man.
PENNY:
No, it wasn't my cat.
(Penny(voice off, ascending the stairs):)It was an experiment designed
by this guy named Schrödinger.
(Eric(appearing round corner with Penny):)From the Charlie Brown cartoons?